Inventory of County trip records from Governor Rampton, 1965-1971.
Utah State Archives and Records Service
Governor Rampton County trip records
1965-1971.
Utah State Archives and Records Service 300 South Rio Grande Salt Lake City, UT 84101-1182 801-533-3535 historyresearch@utah.gov
Series 20902
Governor Rampton
1.00 cubic foot and 2 microfilm reels
This series contains correspondence, schedules, and other information relating to trips that Governor Rampton took to Utah counties from 1965 to 1971. This series includes correspondence from representatives of various counties who often wrote to Rampton's office prior to his trip, detailing issues of concern to that particular county.
Historical Note
An agency history is available.
This series contains correspondence, schedules, and other information relating to trips that Governor Rampton took to Utah counties from 1965 to 1971. This series includes correspondence from representatives of various counties who often wrote to Rampton's office prior to his trip, detailing issues of concern to that particular county.
Chronological by date.
If the date of the is not known, materials are arranged within the year alphabetically by county name. General county trip materials, not specific to individual counties, are filed first under that given year.
This series is classified as Public.
These records were acquired from the creating agency through established retention schedules.
Correspondence from the Governor Rampton, Series 13856, contains more materials related to specific counties.
Material Types; Correspondence
Utah--State-local relations.
Rampton, Calvin L., 1913-2007
- County trip records, 1965-1971.; 1.00 cubic foot and 2 microfilm reels
  - 1965, Schedule of county trips (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1965, Jun 2-4, Washington, Emery, and Carbon Counties (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1965, Jun 24-25, San Juan and Grand Counties (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1965, Jun 29-30, Jul 1-2, Iron, Beaver, Millard, and Juab Counties (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1965, Jul 12-16, Duchesne, Uinta, Daggett, Rich, and Cache Counties (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1965, Aug 10-13, Garfield, Piute, Wayne, Sevier, and Sanpete Counties (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1965, Aug 20, Morgan County (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1965, Aug 24, Weber County (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1965, Aug 31, Davis County (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1965, Sep 3, Box Elder County (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1965, Sep 10, Summit County (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1965, Sep 14, Wasatch County (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1965, Sep 17, Utah County (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1965, Sep 22, Tooele County (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1965, Oct 8, Kane County (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1965, Dec 6, Cache County (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 1965; Salt Lake County, undated trip(s) (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1966, Jul 15, Rich County (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 1967, General (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 1967, Jun 12-16, Millard, Iron, Piute, and Sevier Counties (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 1967, Jul 27, Wasatch County (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 1967, Rich County, undated trip (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 1967-1968, San Juan County, undated trip (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 1967-1968, Sanpete County, undated trip (Reel 1, Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 1967-1968, Weber County, undated trip (Reel 2, Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 1968, General (Reel 2, Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 1968, Jan 31, Uintah County (Reel 2, Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 1968, Morgan County, undated trip (Reel 2, Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 1968, Summit County, undated trip (Reel 2, Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 1968, Tooele County, undated trip (Reel 2, Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 1969, Kane County, undated trip (Reel 2, Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 1969, San Juan County, undated trip (Reel 2, Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 1969, Weber County, undated trip (Reel 2, Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 1971, Emery and Grand Counties, undated trip(s) (Reel 2, Box 1, Folder 34)